Google's AI
is calling you
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
if you're a
homeowner
looking for
someone to
service your
septic system
and you go on
Google
there is a little
button that says
get a quote
and if you push
that button to
get a quote
it's gonna
actually have
Google's AI
voice AI
call four or five
different
businesses it'll
say this is
Google's AI
service and it
will ask for a
quote and then
all the
businesses
whether they
don't respond or
they don't give a
pricing or they
do it's going to
send it back to
the customer
that's out there
looking for
services we just
had our first
client that
actually had a
phone call like
this
so it's still
very much on the
brand new
frontier